<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by fargo.io on Thu, 09 Jan 2014 19:50:32 GMT -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:rss5="http://rss5.org/">
	<channel>
		<title>Dave's Fargo Blog</title>
		<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/</link>
		<description>It's a tradition that when I'm burning in a new blogging tool that I have a &quot;handsome&quot; blog. Of course it's kind of a joke. The blog is in no way handsome at first. The goal is to make it so. ;-)</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 19:50:32 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 19:50:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<generator>Fargo v1.38</generator>
		<docs>http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs>
		<webMaster>dave.winer@gmail.com</webMaster>
		<rss5:account service="twitter">davewiner</rss5:account>
		<rss5:account service="facebook">dave.winer.12</rss5:account>
		<item>
			<title>I'd like this to be an index</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/09/idLikeThisToBeAnIndex.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;One&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Two&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Three&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Four&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 19:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/09/idLikeThisToBeAnIndex.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>30th Anniversary of the Mac</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/03/30thAnniversaryOfTheMac.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;I've been asked to write a piece about the 30th anniversary of the birth of the Macintosh at Flint Center on January 24, 1984. It's quite an honor, a surprising one, because past celebrations of the Mac have been exclusively about the members of the Mac team, and Steve Jobs of course. But things have changed perhaps, and now we can have, hopefully a somewhat more realistic appraisal of the role the Mac played in the evolution of computing, with the benefit of 30 years hindsight.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It was a wonderful day, the culmination of about six months of work by my startup company, Living Videotext, to get a product ready. I had hired my brother and future sister-in-law, to help with the development and rollout. We had a Macintosh in our office, it was a huge secret at the time, but we showed it to our best friends anyway, swearing them to secrecy. I remember my first look at a Macintosh, I knew I was going in to see it, but nothing could prepare me for the surprise, the feeling you get when you look at a baby cat or dog -- this thing is cute and gorgeous and new and filled with potential, and most important it spoke directly to me (and millions of others of course) saying -- use me! &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;That was the brilliance of the Mac, its gestalt. None of the components stood up to the hype. It had nowhere near enough memory. The screen was tiny, as were the floppy disks. The product came at a time when personal computers were getting hard drives, but the Mac had no ability to expand. It didn't even have cursor keys. The Mac was a statement, that's for sure -- but it wasn't a very &lt;i&gt;usable&lt;/i&gt; statement, at least in its first incarnation.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Now that was all fixed, in relatively short order. By 1986 the Mac had arrow keys, a bigger screen, more memory, and most important an expansion capability. Then it was supremely usable, and kicked butt in the market. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;My startup, when the Mac came out, made most of its money off IBM PC software. By 1986, with the help of Bill Campbell at Apple, we got Macs for every employee at our growing company, and our board of directors, and the die was cast -- we became a Mac software company. And we got rich from it. No complaints about that. The Mac was berry berry good to me (a dated reference to a fictional character from the 80s on SNL).&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But what about the long-term historical perspective of the Mac. There, the verdict is not so good. True, all personal computers to follow were basically copies of the Mac, some good, some not so good. I'm typing this on a Mac running software that is an almost exact clone of the software we shipped in 1986 for the Mac. The ideas were very valid, and have stood the test of time. But it's the missed opportunities caused by the Mac's insistence on being right about everything, even when the Mac was wrong, that caused the fractures in the marketplace that are still visible today in the UI of software, and in the confusion of non-expert users. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Try this out sometime with a friend who is a casual computer user who has a WordPress blog. Ask them to choose a command from a menu, and see which one they choose. There are three menu systems on the screen at the same time! One for the operating system, one for the browser, and one for the web app. This is not simple and not easy to use, and is the result of Apple's proprietary networking, way back in the 80s, that forced the innovation in networking, that was the manifest destiny of personal computers, to route around the closed-off networking protocols of the Macintosh. Had Apple, instead of keeping the right to create networking software for itself almost exclusively, because their APIs were so incomprehensible and contradictory, taken the opposite approach -- that their APIs were not proprietary and could be cloned by other manufacturers freely, and built on by software developers, again, freely, the networks we use today would work in vastly different and imho, much better ways. We'd also be much further along. In many ways, the networking user interfaces we use today are inferior to the ones we used on the Mac in the 80s -- thirty years later! So we haven't even progressed over all that time, we're still struggling to re-invent the basic UI techniques we had working back then. It's a miracle that you can use an outliner in the browser as I am right now, but wait a minute -- we had that working in 1984. If only Steve and Sidhu et al hadn't been so possessive. And if you think I didn't say anything about this at the time, you don't know me very well. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;There were a handful of companies that had mastered the Apple networking stack at the time. Reese Jones' Farallon, Andrew Singer's Think Technologies. A pair of developers who made an email app the was bought by Microsoft and became their mail product (the founder of that company, Steve Ullman, was a real visionary). And Don Brown at CE Software with QuickMail. I tried to work with all of them, but it wasn't enough of a critical mass to make a market. I deperately wanted networking for MORE, my outliner. I felt it wasn't complete without it. Had Apple been less restrictive, my career would have been much more interesting. We have the networking today that I wanted then. But it was a long time coming. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The web should have happened on the Mac. We had the best software, the best developers, the best platform, no 640K limit (don't laugh, software on the PC was limited in how far it could grow). We had it all, but the Apple culture wouldn't let us use it.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I love the Mac. I love what it did for me, it gave me a lot of freedom I wouldn't have gotten any other way. However, it stopped short of where it could have gone, and in doing so, I hope serves as a lesson for future generations of technologists. When someone argues for reserving the best stuff for your employees, tell them to stop screwing with your success. As the famous Apple evangelist Guy Kawasaki said, Let a thousand flowers bloom. Love the developers and the random chaos the bring to you, and be ready for the love that will flow around your platform. It's the only way that works.&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 14:49:06 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/03/30thAnniversaryOfTheMac.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>What would a &quot;public notepad&quot; do?</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/01/whatWouldAPublicNotepadDo.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2013/12/31/twitterAsANotepad&quot;&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; about using Twitter as a &quot;public notepad.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Sure, the note-putting part of it was great. One item after another in rapid-fire, with the ability of people to add or comment. Most of it was pretty civil because.. Well I don't know why. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But when it came time to gather it all up and present it as a matter of record, that was a lot of hard work, and the result wasn't very satisfying. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;So how would it work?&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 21:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2014/01/01/whatWouldAPublicNotepadDo.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Twitter as a public notepad</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/31/twitterAsANotepad.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;I don't know what came over me this morning, but I got an idea after watching a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PqPCiKFmGjM&quot;&gt;speech&lt;/a&gt; by Elizabeth Warren on YouTube. I was in tears, the ideas were so simple and compelling, and so rarely talked about. We are a country of people, not corporations -- but we've lost track of that, and we're stacking the deck against the people. But then I remembered, she hasn't said anything about the NSA spying on the American people. One idea led to another, and people responded, and I kept going. I wanted to get all of it down here in one place, before moving on into 2014. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Watching Elizabeth Warren's speech at the DNC, literally in tears she's so great, except -- what has she said about NSA spying on Americans?&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Same thing with Ezra Klein. What an up-and-comer. So smart. Always has the right answer. Except on NSA spying on Americans. Crickets.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I live a few blocks from Times Square. It's already crazy here. Why do people stand in the street? Most don't get to see the ball drop.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;My opinion about the NSA. Politics in the US stops until it's over. Nothing. It's unacceptable. Outrageous. Fascist. Un-American.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The @paulg story is opportunism by Gawker and this new publication. Headline should read: Graham is not a politician. That's the real story.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Truth: @paulg has a narrow view of who can make a contribution in tech. However: That's his right as an investor and human being.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;For example, I'd like @paulg to tell the students who come to Startup School that being an entrepreneur isn't the only way to contribute.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I was forced to be an entrepreneur when I was young because there was no other way to be creative. Wasn't a good fit. Yet I did contribute.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's always been a struggle. To this day people describe me as an entrepreneur. I am not an entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;People say I'm a lousy entrepreneur. True! I'm also a lousy polo player.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;If I were in my teens today, Zuck would not be my role model.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;You know who would be my role model? Banksy! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Evan Williams is an entrepreneur. Aaron Levie is an entrepreneur. James Hong. Nothing wrong with being an entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But -- don't expect entrepreneurs to love your creativity. It's not what they do.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;One of the good things about the Gawker-created mess is that we can talk about @paulg. In other times, VCs are very much a forbidden topic.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Online discourse would work better if it was always understood that there's a difference between The Truth and Your Opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's time for the Knicks to call Phil Jackson. &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 23:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/31/twitterAsANotepad.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blogging matters</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/30/peopleDontUnderstandBlogging.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;I read a &lt;a href=&quot;http://ofcourseitsaboutyou.com/2013/08/11/the-effects-of-nursing-on-nurses/&quot;&gt;long post&lt;/a&gt; this morning about what it's like to be a nurse, and found it incredibly interesting. It filled in a perspective that I had not heard. And yet I spent lots of time talking with nurses during my father's long hospital stay in 2002, and my own -- the same year. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Back then, I had an epiphany about people who work in hospitals, who work in conditions most of us find incomprehensible, helping people in unimaginable pain, unimaginable until it's time for you to deal with it. The epiphany is that it must be wonderful to see the good you do, so clearly. In my own field, software development, it can be hard to feel how you're helping. In fact you get a lot of people sharing pain with you they can't find other outlets for. I learned in reading the post that it's the same in nursing. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;While their work is gratifying and grounding, it's also grueling and abusive. She told the story so well, so personally. Yet in the comments people found many things to complain about. She just shared her point of view, wrote a blog post, and it was good, and of course the trolls gave her hell for it.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's important to feel free to tell your story even if it cues up other people's permission to be jerks. Oh this person is showing vulnerability. Let's make her pay! I get it all the time. I've been getting it since I started blogging in 1994. I still do it, because it's what I do. I couldn't stop, even though I've tried, any more than I could stop breathing. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I don't have a solution, other than to say it helps to stand beside people who put themselves out there. The world is rough. That doesn't mean you can't share what you see. It just means it's important to feel the support. I want to provide what little of that I can, through this post.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;What bloggers are guilty of -- always -- is telling their story imperfectly. It's the imperfections that make it interesting, and human -- and worth it. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Keep on truckin!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's not like anyone gets out of this alive. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&quot;cheesecake&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:20:58 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/30/peopleDontUnderstandBlogging.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Time waits for no one</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/29/timeWaitsForNoOne.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Robert Morse, the actor who plays &lt;a href=&quot;http://madmen.wikia.com/wiki/Bertram_Cooper&quot;&gt;Bert Cooper&lt;/a&gt; on Mad Men was the star of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/How_to_Succeed_in_Business_Without_Really_Trying&quot;&gt;How To Succeed in Business Without Really Trying&lt;/a&gt;, which was a hit musical from the 1960s. It was both a Broadway play and a movie.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dl.dropbox.com/s/xnveudb1vo6pteb/bert.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dl.dropbox.com/s/ymbicx5zz6gt6ml/howtosucceed.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;This came up in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/michael.swaine/posts/10151771478340426&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on Facebook by Michael Swaine. He wondered how a young fan of Mad Men would feel about this. I suggested they might listen to an old &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4TeR7P7pDxk&quot;&gt;Rolling Stones&lt;/a&gt; song. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Here's something really twisted about Robert Morse/Bert Cooper. The movie, How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying came out in 1967, which is roughly the time when Mad Men was taking place. The world of Sterling Cooper is contemporary with the movie. That's a mind bomb. I'm sure the people who made the TV show are aware of this. I'm surprised they didn't have the movie show up in the story of the TV show. Wouldn't it be cool if an actor playing Robert Morse had met Bert Cooper? Would the world have blown up? Is that like the butterfly in the famous Ray Bradbury &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Sound_of_Thunder&quot;&gt;short story&lt;/a&gt;? O the humanity!&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 22:34:03 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/29/timeWaitsForNoOne.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tech products of the year</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/29/techProductsOfTheYear.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;This year's &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2013/12/26/boty&quot;&gt;BOTY&lt;/a&gt; choice was such a big hit, the idea crossed my mind that I have a couple of products that distinguished themselves in my life in 2013, and what the heck, why not have a POTY to go with the BOTY! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The thought came to me while I was on a walk today in Central Park, listening to Grateful Dead music through one of the products, and played by the other one. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I said man, I finally have this figured out after many years of walking and listening, I have a rig that's worth talking about it's so good.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;First the headphones. I like to say I buy headphones the way some women I've known buy shoes. I have a closet shelf full of them. Most of them I tried out for a few days or maybe a week or two and put them away, still in search of the ideal set. &lt;img style=&quot;float: right; margin-left: 25px; margin-bottom: 15px;&quot; src=&quot;http://static.scripting.com/larryKing/images/2013/12/29/velodyne.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But after I bought the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00A6YPCK8/ref=wms_ohs_product?ie=UTF8&amp;psc=1&quot;&gt;Velodyne vFree&lt;/a&gt; headphones I not only stopped buying new phones, I starting giving the old ones away to friends. And these were some great listening devices. But none of them put it all together like the Velodyne.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;First, they are wireless Bluetooth headphones. You wouldn't believe how much of a mess those wires are for me. Always getting tangled and knotted. Limiting movement. Pulling on my ears and the device. Now I look at people listening on their iPods on the subway and think that in two years the wires will all be gone. Once you try it this way there's no going back. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Also, they're loud enough, and the sound quality is great. A lot of good headphones need an amplifier when used with a mobile device. Not sure why, but it's observable. I guess these headphones, because they have their own power source, have their own amp. Regardless, you don't miss anything with these guys, and music has the feel it's supposed to. And it's a clean sound, maybe a little heavy on the bass, but I like that anyway. But not so much as some &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.beatsbydre.com/&quot;&gt;others&lt;/a&gt;. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Now there are problems with wireless. You have to remember to keep it charged. But that's a discipline we've all learned by now. It's just one more device. It takes the same kind of USB cable that Kindles and Google phones do. You probably already have a few. And the Bluetooth connection sometimes drops, but for some reason for me now not so much as it did in the beginning. It feels like my devices have learned how to find each other. I know that can't be true, but...&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;#### Product #2&lt;img style=&quot;float: right; margin-left: 25px; margin-bottom: 15px;&quot; src=&quot;http://static.scripting.com/larryKing/images/2013/12/29/ipadMiniRetina2013.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Now the other device is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://store.apple.com/us/buy-ipad/ipad-mini-retina/64gb-space-gray-wifi-cellular-verizon&quot;&gt;new iPad Mini&lt;/a&gt;. I got one with 64GB and LTE. I used Verizon because I already have a T-Mobile device (my Nexus 5), and this gives me a bit of redundancy that may come in handy. Both devices tether. Glad we got over that argument! ;-) &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I bought an iPad Air when it came out and loved it, but that got handed down, because I very much wanted to try an iPad that fits in my jacket pocket, which the Mini most definitely does. I miss the larger screen sometimes, but I love the portability. With a few tweaks, I can see not carrying a phone. But remember, it's winter and cold, so I'm pretty much always wearing a jacket. We'll see how it works in summer, when I'm back doing daily bike rides in summer clothes. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But the iPad Air is as rational and lovely a product as the Velodyne, and of course the two go together perfectly, and connect over an open standard, so it's a religion-conformant combination. At the end of the year, it's clear that these two products made the most difference to me, and appeal to my tastes and lifestyle almost perfectly. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It might get better in 2014, I hope so, but it was worth noting that near-perfection has been achieved this year. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;BTW, when I bought the Velodyne in April I paid $299. They're selling on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00A6YPCK8/ref=wms_ohs_product?ie=UTF8&amp;psc=1&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; now for $119. Wow. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;PS: As I am working on the transition to a new CMS, I'm producing some blog posts in both environments, to get experience, and get a sense of what features are needed. Here's the &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/misc/fargoTestBlog/2013/12/29/techProductsOfTheYear.html&quot;&gt;new version&lt;/a&gt; of this post, in case you're interested in such things. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 16:54:12 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/29/techProductsOfTheYear.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>GitHub Pages are great!</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/28/githubPagesWorks.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;In November I wrote a blog post &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2013/11/22/specASimpleDropboxbasedWebService&quot;&gt;asking&lt;/a&gt; for a simple web server connected to Dropbox. I needed this for the upcoming version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://fargo.io/&quot;&gt;Fargo&lt;/a&gt;. We've been looking since then, and now we have an answer.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Pages service&lt;/a&gt; does what we need. GitHub will be hard for some users, but it's a beginning. We'll make it easier. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;BTW, this page is on my &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.github.io/virginBlog/2013/12/28/githubPagesWorks.html&quot;&gt;GitHub-hosted site&lt;/a&gt;.  :-) &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 18:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/28/githubPagesWorks.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>I love Central Park</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/26/iLoveCentralPark.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;A little over two years ago I decided to move uptown, and up in the air -- out of the East Village where it was noisy and I had to ride all the way cross-town to get on the Hudson River bike trail. One of the things I didn't figure in was that living close to Central Park would make a big difference. It really does.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Walking in Manhattan seemed like it must be a dream, when I lived in Berkeley. Every day I could walk a different set of streets. It would take forever until I had walked the same street twice. But it's not so simple. There are so many people on the streets in NYC, you can't space out and just walk, like you can in Berkeley, even though there isn't much variety there (it's all gorgeous, which can get really boring after a while). The best answer is Central Park! Where yes, sometimes it gets really crowded, but there are so many walking paths, so many different places to go, especially in the winter, you can often get away from all the hustle and bustle, even while still being in the greatest city in America. It's a pretty good deal. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It was masterfully designed many years ago by &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frederick_Law_Olmsted&quot;&gt;Olmstead&lt;/a&gt;. It's evolved over the years, but it has &quot;good bones&quot; and a philosophy that's stood the test of time. It's a democratizing space, used by all classes of people, where we all meet and hang out. Yes it's NY, not New Orleans, so people don't engage that much with each other, but just being in proximity, while recreating and relaxing, is worth a lot. &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 16:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/26/iLoveCentralPark.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>This is what Scripting News will look like.</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/24/thisIsWhatScriptingNewsWillLookLike.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;You're reading this on a test blog. But the software I'm using will become the CMS of &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/&quot;&gt;Scripting News&lt;/a&gt;, as well as the CMS that's attached to &lt;a href=&quot;http://fargo.io/&quot;&gt;Fargo&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I've been working on a new design of the internal CMS since the &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2013/10/07/endOfTrex&quot;&gt;meltdown&lt;/a&gt; of the Trex server in early October. This new CMS is not as easy to use as Trex, but I hope it will eventually be as easy. It is a much more reliable architecture because it does not rely at all on a central server. The entire CMS runs inside Fargo, on the user's local machine. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's basically the same architecture we used for &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radio_UserLand&quot;&gt;Radio UserLand&lt;/a&gt; in 2002, except instead of requiring you to install an app, the CMS is in the browser. It's a whole new way to do it, and it works well enough now that I can blog with it. However there's still more work to do to get it so that it can manage Scripting News, and then more work after that to make it user-friendly. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;This is my pre-Christmas message. There will be more to say about it over time.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static.scripting.com/larryKing/images/2013/12/24/tree.gif&quot; width=&quot;145&quot; height=&quot;185&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;A picture named tree.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Ho ho ho!&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 15:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/24/thisIsWhatScriptingNewsWillLookLike.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Roast post</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/20/roastPost.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;abc&quot;scripting news&quot;def&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Yesssxxxs oo &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/corikesler/posts/10201758540419122?notif_t=close_friend_activity&quot;&gt;ssssppprrrssy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I just changed the way menu layout works. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;fuzzy wu &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/corikesler/posts/10201758540419122?notif_t=close_friend_activity&quot;&gt;zzy&lt;/a&gt; wasn't fuzzy was he?&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I'm dreaming of a White Christmas!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;%appConsts.productname%&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;%socialMediaStinks ()%&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;This is a test of a glossary entry with a bit of Markdown in it.&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 18:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/20/roastPost.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why doesn't Snowden blog?</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/19/whyDoesntEdwardSnowdenHaveABlog.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Everything  we hear from and about Snowden, since the initial interviews, and the online Q&amp;As, has come through filters. We learn a lot from the news reports, but his perspective was adding a lot, as well. We could use the perspective of someone who has worked inside the NSA. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Since no one else is coming forward, it would be great if Snowden could &lt;i&gt;personally&lt;/i&gt; join the discussion. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Update #1: The first things Snowden said after becoming famous were amazingly clear and challenging. He called bullshit on the tech companies, and they're still bullshitting. If they really cared about the NSA tapping their lines, they would stop it. What they don't like is the &lt;i&gt;publicity&lt;/i&gt; about it. I can say that all I want and no one will care, but he has an amazing pulpit. And I suspect he doesn't really have a clear picture of how little information is trickling out to the people based on his leaks, and how the perspective lacks his sharpness and clarity. If he understood, he might have something to say. Imho.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Update #2: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/balleyne/status/414046100358574081&quot;&gt;Blaise Alleyne&lt;/a&gt; had the answer -- &quot;I thought Snowden had restrictions on his ability to speak out as part of his conditions of Russian asylum.&quot; That's absolutely correct. I had forgotten that. &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 22:11:29 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/19/whyDoesntEdwardSnowdenHaveABlog.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kids use calculators?</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/18/kidsUseCalculators.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;I've been working at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nypl.org/&quot;&gt;NYPL&lt;/a&gt; lately because of construction noise in my apartment building. It's a great place to work. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Quiet,  and lots of good people watching. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I saw this student working problems on his VAIO laptop, and what is that black thing with the red arrow pointing to it? It's a calculator.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I used one of those in freshman year in college, but I assumed that students these days would use something on their computer.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Surprised!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;PS: Here's an Amazon &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=nb_sb_ss_c_0_21?url=search-alias%3Delectronics&amp;field-keywords=scientific+calculator&amp;sprefix=scientific+calculator%2Caps%2C136&amp;rh=n%3A172282%2Ck%3Ascientific+calculator&quot;&gt;search&lt;/a&gt; for scientific calculators. They're affordable! &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 00:52:48 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/18/kidsUseCalculators.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>It was icy today</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/16/itWasIcyToday.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Cold, **beautiful** -- quiet. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;My new  software, in development, makes me want to write. That has not happened in a long time. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I want to write for my own purposes, but never because the software makes me happy. This time is different. &lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 21:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/16/itWasIcyToday.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Adam Curry in the 80s</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/adamCurryInThe80s.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Adam just posted this picture on Twitter, but I saw it on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;He says there's so much going on in this picture. I wonder what?&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;He's got a nice DJ setup. Lots of nice toys. He seems intent.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;What else do you see?&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 14:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/adamCurryInThe80s.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Where's The Beef?</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/wheresTheBeef.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;This was  a great &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Where%27s_the_beef%3F&quot;&gt;ad&lt;/a&gt; for Wendy's in 1984.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;420&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/Ug75diEyiA0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clara_Peller&quot;&gt;Clara Peller&lt;/a&gt;, the little o ld lady on the right, wants to know where the other burger guys (presumably McDonald's and Burger King) hid the beef. It's true. Their burgers had a lot of lettuce and sauce and bread, but not all that much beef. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&quot;I don't think there's anyone back there,&quot; she said. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;This became a cultural touchstone.  When you thought someone was bullshitting you, you'd say &lt;i&gt;Where's The Beef, &lt;/i&gt;and everyone would think of the cute old grandma, and have a nice laugh.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;So the question is this -- if you said &lt;i&gt;Where's The Beef &lt;/i&gt;to a young person today would they know WTF you're talking about?&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 14:13:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/wheresTheBeef.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bargniani!</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/bargniani.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;Hey the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Andrea_Bargnani&quot;&gt;guy&lt;/a&gt; finally woke up and scored some points last night.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;And I completely dig the way Walt Clyde Frazier pronounces his name. As if it were &lt;i&gt;Bar-gniar-nee. &lt;/i&gt;He puts a whole R in there that isn't actually in his name.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Now J.R. Smith wasn't playing too good, so he sulked on the bench.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;While Tyson Chandler cheered the team on from the sidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;But this story isn't about Chandler. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;It's about Bargniarnie. My pal. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 13:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/15/bargniani.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dick Van Dyke?</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/13/dickVanDyke.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;First, I gotta say upfront that I think Julie Andrews  is super  sexy. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I know I know it’s weird, but I do!  So  I thought it would be a good idea, with the new Tom Hanks/Emma Thompson movie  coming out, to wa tch Mary Poppins, just so I’d have a full context on what the fight was about.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Well I found the movie almost unwatchable because Dick Van Dyk plays some kind of British street person. It makes my teeth hurt like someone running their fingernails on the blackboard.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Should I just skip over the scenes he’s in? Why is he needed anyway? I don’t get it. The movie is about kids, magic, and most of all JULIE ANDREWS!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Please explain. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 18:18:33 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/13/dickVanDyke.html</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>This is a test</title>
			<link>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/11/thisIsATest.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;p&gt;I am  writing a blog post. But I haven't set it up yet to publish so this should not publish.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;And sure enough it did not publish. That's good. Now I'm going to try turning it on and see what ha ppens. &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;don't blink&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I  miss  the earth so muc h I  miss  my wife.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt; It's lonely ou t in space.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Let's  see if  we  get the bread   crumbs.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;%byline ()%&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;xxx ()&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;rssLink&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;uncle davey had a  tree.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;google ana lyti cs&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;%new Date ()%&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 17:14:58 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>http://virgin.smallpict.com/2013/12/11/thisIsATest.html</guid>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>
